testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Ah,
Hi.
I finished the radio show
and turned on the live
in the car.
But
right now
I'm holding it almost like I'm taking a selfie
so it might be a bit shaky.
Please understand.
Did you enjoy the radio show?
It felt like
it went by
so fast and frantically.
I'm alone in the car right now.
It's a shame but
it's so funny that the members didn't know about the Starex incident.
I mean
we talked about it
quite a lot though
so I can't believe
they didn't know.
But these days
wherever we go
that story
always comes up.
It's so funny.
It's so funny that it's been going on for 3 years.
Yesterday what we talked about yesterday the dream
the dream really
what we talked about
besides that
there was
more
but I can't remember.
I forgot.
I was like
wow this is so fascinating
I have to tell them about this
but
like a Q&A
there's a questionnaire
like this
and
two blanks
at the bottom that you had to fill in.
It was something like that.
The questions were like that.
So
I was thinking hasn't the week ended yet
I had thoughts like that
and as soon as I woke up
uh
why does my body
ache so much?
Fan meeting
Here
as we pass by
each wall
color
my face
looks different
Yellow
It's like doing a personal
color
diagnosis
with random lighting right.
Right now
the radio show is over and I'm
getting off work.
Today
I wanted to call my mom yesterday but I was so tired
so I couldn't call her back.
I need to call her back
today
Today
I'll probably
go home
and get some good
rest right?
I have to go
do
the
chores
that I haven't
finished.
My house is so messy.
Thinking of changing it tomorrow?
Yeah,
I did think about that a bit today. What should I do tomorrow?
Ah but
I thought these long
nails
would be uncomfortable
so I've only been doing
short ones
but now that I've done it they're so pretty.
Yeah. So this time
I'm thinking of doing
a different
vibe
maybe a refreshing vibe
I'm thinking
about it.
Give me some recommendations.
Unnie seriously
I thought you had the face
to easily pass a meeting with the in-laws.
Oh
no.
I really thought
I had that kind of face too
but
ah my hair color right now
is a bit like this
so excluding this
if it was black
and
I said hello Mother like this
wouldn't this be
a free pass
face?
Ah so Chaeyoung must have
felt like this.
Let's move on. That wasn't funny.
My mom says she likes it.
What should I eat
for lunch
today?
Actually
that
while doing music shows
I couldn't really eat much.
Even if I ate I only ate a little bit
and
psychologically
a bit
these
outfits
show a lot of skin so
I couldn't eat much
but today
I want to try eating something delicious.
Recommend me
something really
really delicious
Mala Xiangguo sounds delicious too.
Wow the chat is so fast.
No. Food that
we eat a lot
while working
because of that
a bit
those
in the car
or outside
things that are hard to eat
in waiting rooms
and places like that
things that you have to set up a big meal for
recommend me things like that.
Shabu-shabu
sounds delicious too.
Gamjatang.
Gamjatang
sounds delicious too.
Galbijjim.
I'll
eat today
since so many
different menus are coming up right now
I'll eat
and share what I ate
with you guys.
Gopchang jeongol sounds delicious too.
Why do the corners of my eyes
feel so
raised today?
Puppy
or cat.
Ah
tunnel that tunnel
Oh my
I keep lying down
this chair
is making this a lying down broadcast.
Chaeyoung isn't in the back
right now.
Ah today is Monday.
I didn't know.
Which Monday?
Monday.
Have a good Monday
cheer up. I was so
out of touch with
the day and time
that I just turned this on
thinking I'm done with work
and turned it on.
Right now
sorry.
Just bear with me for a bit.
Looking at it like this it really looks like short hair. Right
Wrong.
But looking at this hair color it really gives the vibe
from the Stay This Way era.
Ah I was going to say something earlier
it's Monday.
Have a great Monday.
Monday
Music Core MC
was fun.
The concept was so
so cute.
Kind of like the Kasukabe
Defense Group
vibe.
So I told the members
let's do it with that vibe.
Like the Kasukabe Defense Group
let's try it
I said. Next week wait this week too
did you
guys know?
This week too
we're doing the special MC.
You didn't know.
You didn't know. It hasn't been announced yet.
I didn't know either.
If you didn't know
then I can't help it.
How
to take back
the words I spilled?
Uh.
But I seriously got LASIK yet
I somehow
out of habit
look at things closely.
I can see everything like this too but
you know what this is? It's a habit.
And I don't know why but
my eyes
got worse.
I can't see well. Not as well as
at first.
Is it normally like this?
But
they said my astigmatism
is a bit severe.
Way worse
than average so
a little
I feel like I might have to
do it once more. LASIK
I think I might have to do LASIK
once more.
Right it's because I wear contacts a lot. These days
even if I wear
soft
contacts
my eyes get so dry so
I end up using
really
a lot of artificial tears.
How many eggs do you put in Neoguri?
I'm really
curious. I'm so
curious about this.
I put in two.
Just
the number of ramen
packs
plus
one.
If I cook two
I put in three
if I cook three I put in four
but I haven't cooked three yet.
It's because I like eggs.
But among
all the ramen I like Neoguri the best.
So the two combine
but
how could it not be tasty.
Why
do people say it doesn't match
and
stuff?
Putting eggs in Neoguri is delicious.
Why do they say not to do that?
The people who say not to do that must be saying it
after trying it right.
That's a bit
putting eggs in Neoguri even for me is a bit
What's the reason? Just
because it doesn't match
ah respect preferences ah I'm just asking because I'm curious too.
Eggs are drawn on the ramen packet. Right.
Ramen that has eggs drawn on the packet is tasty when you add eggs.
And the ones without it are tasty as they are. I know that too but
but
it goes well together.
Neoguri
I mean
whether it's Neoguri
or whatever
just having eggs
in ramen itself
in spicy red ramen
Ah
they think the egg ruins
Neoguri's clean
seafood broth taste.
That's really a matter of preference.
I'm going to keep
putting it in.
Because it's delicious.
That's it.
You tell me to
put cheese in but I
I
don't really like cheese in my ramen. I don't like cheese that much.
Even on things like steamed egg
I don't like it when there's cheese on top
so I scrape off the cheese a bit when I eat.
So it must be that kind of feeling.
Mmhmm.
I don't
scramble the eggs in it.
That's a bit much.
Ah right
even like this
like this
I can see if I look closely.
But for LASIK
did I
ever talk about
my LASIK experience?
I
went in the morning
and did it
but I did really well.
Somehow my
eyes were a bit
complexly
bad
should I say? Things were mixed up so
it was a bit hard
but the doctor
told me not to be nervous
and just keep staring
straight ahead.
So I was doing that
and things were coming right up
close to me.
But it wasn't
that scary.
It didn't hurt
either.
But right after it ended and I came out
trying to go home
I couldn't open my eyes. Tears kept coming out like this
so I was like this
couldn't even open my eyes and
the manager
came to get me and I went in the car like this
went home
turned off all the lights
laid in bed
and slept
while crying.
Going it hurts so much
I think right after it finished
is when it hurt
for me.
Really
but they said it hurts for about
four hours after it ends.
So
I took medicine
took painkillers
and
just slept for exactly four hours
straight away.
But right until I fell asleep
it was seriously
a pain
I had never experienced before.
Usually even if you
get a shot
you get it in your arm
or somewhere like that
there aren't many times
your eyes hurt.
But having pain
inside
your eyes is such a
fascinating
experience. For me
I mean ah
it felt even more
painful.
But
I
tried it myself.
I totally recommend it.
Saying you won't do it
because you're scared is
foolish.
It's not at all
that level of
fear or
pain.
Of course
it depends on what you do
but I completely
want to tell people
to do it.
If it's necessary.
The recovery period doesn't take long either. On that day
I slept and woke up and immediately
spent about two days
in a slightly blurry
state
and after that I was fine. Even contacts
I wear them comfortably
now just that it got a bit dry
that's all.
Mmhmm.
Right now
the right side
is blooming with grass so it's dark
my face doesn't look pretty
Recently I went to get dental treatment
honestly the fear of the dentist
is really
something
everyone of all ages has.
For me
it was so bad that
I was even
asking ChatGPT
I
have to go to the dentist but I'm so so scared. What do I do?
Can't I do sleep anesthesia? I was even asking
things like that.
Because I was so scared.
But
I got it done well.
I'm
fine
with shots.
I'm fine with anesthesia
and things like that
but I really hate that chilling sensation.
That's the most
painful.
Scary.
The sound and all that is fine.
I have to go get my wisdom teeth pulled.
This might sound
a bit weird but
I've pulled out all four of my wisdom teeth.
I don't have any left.
But
after pulling out
the wisdom teeth
your cheeks swell up
like Moomin.
I found that so funny
that I wish I had a few more wisdom teeth.
Do you
know what I mean?
Ah maybe not?
I wish
I had just one more. I don't have any?
But wisdom teeth
did hurt a bit I think.
With wisdom teeth
tears
fall down like this again
too.
Thanks for
respecting
my preferences.
You're saying
you'll write it
on Namuwiki.
On Namuwiki can
anyone just write things? Can I write on my own page too?
Then
oh
I can.
Really
then what if someone writes weird things on it?
Can I just go in
and edit it myself?
Then can I
change my name
to something other than Lee Nagyung too?
Ah the history all shows up.
Have I ever talked about this?
In
middle school
I wanted to change
my name.
Have I talked about this?
Uh.
Ah.
Oh. I did talk about it.
Then should I not talk about it?
Then
I won't talk about it.
For those who are curious
go look it up.
Who pretended to know?
But it's really nothing special.
I originally
didn't know
the name. Just
actually there's no special reason.
Back then
my mindset was
let's live with a new
reborn
mindset.
It was middle school syndrome.
Let's live anew
I thought
and while thinking about what to do
I was thinking
isn't there something
that not many people
use?
I wondered if I should use
the letter 'U'
And my parents also
gave me the okay.
From what I remember.
But
I don't know.
Somehow
as time passed
I ended up not doing it.
Why was it
the reason?
That was
my thought back then.
I don't know about now but
you know
when you say something
in English
like I love you
like this
That
that 'You'
feels like
everyone's
name should I say?
Do you know what I mean?
You probably don't know
what I'm saying. I don't really know
either.
Just
says I love you
if someone
it means they're saying
they love me
right.
At the time that just felt very meaningful to me.
You know what I mean right?
Cute
it was cute.
But right now
honestly
I have no thoughts
of changing my name
making a stage name
now would be funny too
suddenly
suddenly showing up
with a different name would be funny though.
But I like my name. The meaning is good and
the pronunciation
me and Chaeyoung
did the Pretty Age 25
challenge
go look it up.
Because we're not
25 years old
anymore.
Even at most
we're not 25.
But the nickname
Nakko that I made
when I was really young
wait not until now. Just
the fact that so many people
still call me that is nice
somehow
should I say it feels refreshing?
It's a bit fascinating.
Would the
Nagyung
from back then
have known?
That I'd
be called this now
for 20
wait 27 years
The members
really don't call me
by my name
Even usually
when they call me
they don't say Nagyung-ah
they say Kkoya
Kkoya
Nakko-ya
Hayoung Unnie says
Na Nakko-ya
like this
saying Kkoya Nakko-ya
and Chaeyoung and
Jiwon Unnie just go Kkoya Kkoya like this
and Jiheon
ah Jiheon calls me Nagyung Unnie.
Anyway guys
it was short
woah it's too dark.
It was short but
I had fun.
It was meaningful.
Let's meet again next time.
I'm a puppy-cat today.
It's puppy-cat makeup.
Why am I so puffy today?
Bye.
I'll come back
soon.
Bye.
M.